Amechare Self-Made Interviews
Amechare Self-Made Interview
So, this time, of course, we have this person here with us.
This is Hana Kojima from Amechare Flash.
I'm Hana Kojima. Nice to meet you.
Pretty for you
Let's make it happen with you.
I'll start now.
If it's a meaningless word, I won't put it in anymore
It's a now, it's a vow
You and me so
Okay, so my first question is this.
What was your dream when you were a child?
When I was little, my dream was not to be an idol or anything like that.
I always wanted to be an Italian chef.
If I was going to be a chef, I thought it would be an Italian restaurant that made pizza, which I love.
What made you fall in love with pizza in the first place?
I don't know why.
I don't know why, but I really thought I liked pizza before I knew it.
I used to go out to eat with my grandma.
There was a pizza place near my grandma's house
I used to go there a lot.
I think that's how I came to like her.
Also, I think Yuka Kojimaki likes to order pizza and delivery pizza.
She often ordered pizza for delivery.
That's why I've been eating pizza since I was a kid.
I thought maybe that's why she fell in love with it.
There was one more thing I wanted to be.
I wanted to be a chef.
But when I was a kid, I didn't really know what chef meant.
Just because the word "chef" is similar to "chef".Just because I'm a chef and the word is similar.
Chef and I wanted to be a chef, that was my childhood dream.
I see. So that was your childhood dream.
Then, what is your dream now?
To sing the theme song of One Piece.
Wow, that's amazing!
I can't let anyone take that away from me.
I love One Piece so much.
One Piece has really helped me in my life.
If you ask me if it's really my textbook, I'll tell you it's One Piece.
I also looked at the textbooks at school.
One Piece has become a very important part of my life.
What is your favorite scene in One Piece?
I don't know...
My personal favorite scene is...
The scene in volume 8 where Luffy punches Don Creek.
But he doesn't just hit him.
There is someone called Don Creek.
He's wearing a cloak with a kenzan needle barred on it.
He's protecting himself with a
I thought I couldn't hit him.
So Luffy punches him in the face.
I was surprised that there is a hero who can do such a thing.
This is my favorite scene.
What are you going to do to sing the theme song of One Piece?
I'm going to say out loud that I love One Piece.
I think that by saying out loud that I love One Piece, it will catch someone's attention.
I also think it's important for Amefurashi to become famous.
One Piece is a very popular anime.
If you become a famous artist
I think that if I become a famous artist, I could be entrusted with the theme song.I'm wondering if I can be trusted with the theme song.
Not by myself, but as part of Amefurashi.
I'd like to sing the theme song for One Piece.
But it's a very difficult dream, isn't it?
One Piece is coming to an end.
I need to hurry up!
Also, I hear you've been pretty busy lately.
What do you do on your days off?
Of course I read One Piece on my day off.
I love to go to Disney.
I like Disney very much.
Lately, whenever I have a day off, I go to Disney.
I like Disney so much that I go there whenever I have a free time.
But I don't have a pass this year and I'm really sad.
I wish they would bring back the annual pass very soon.
Do you have any recommendations on how to enjoy Disney?
I want to enjoy everything, so I go around very efficiently.
I want to go here, take a picture here, eat here.
I want to go to the next attraction.
I love to make my schedule very efficient.
When I went to Yukiniland with the first group of Namie girls
I think I was able to lead the group
I think I was able to take the lead.
And Kojima-san, I heard you have some ambitions.
Can I ask you for a favor?
Yes, I want to be the ace of AmeFlash.
I think some of you are laughing right now.
I'm answering seriously.
The ace of the group right now is Airou, the center of the group.
I'm sure you all think that this is unshakable, right?
But 5 years from now, I will be the ace of AmeflashBut five years from now I'll be an ace at Ameflash.
I think Airan will be standing in the position of the flower.
So, can I say something to Aira, who is probably watching this?
Yes, I do.
Hey, Airan!
I'm sure you're just relaxing there for now.
Five years from now
I'll be the girl of the moment!
What? A girl of the moment?
Yes, I knew it!
The ace in the hole is the girl of the moment.
I'm not like this, after all.
I want to prove that even Kojima Hana can be a modern girl.
I'd like to prove it!
So, thank you very much for your valuable talk today.
Thank you very much.
And that's our guest this time, Ms. Hana Kojima from Ameflas!